<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>How to on 0800 BEN</title>
    <link>http://0800ben.com/how_to/</link>
    <description>Recent content in How to on 0800 BEN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 18:48:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://0800ben.com/how_to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Safehouse Nightmare</title>
      <link>http://0800ben.com/how_to/safehouse_nightmare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://0800ben.com/how_to/safehouse_nightmare/</guid>
      <description>Safehouse Nightmare: A shallow diveSo apparently completing everything at Mayhem difficulty INCLUDES safehouse nightmare. Whose idea was that? Anyway here&amp;rsquo;s a braindump of info about safehouse nightmare followed by some (probably trash tier) builds. If you don&amp;rsquo;t want to read I can confirm that as of like Feb 2023 the turret cheese strat still works. If you want a cakewalk, do that.
The HeistThe main gimmick of this heist is that you have to survive for 6 minutes while being assaulted by Cloakers and Headless Bulldozers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First turn kill bosses in Bravely Default 2</title>
      <link>http://0800ben.com/how_to/first_turn_kill_bosses_in_bravely_default2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://0800ben.com/how_to/first_turn_kill_bosses_in_bravely_default2/</guid>
      <description>First Turn Kill (Almost) All Bosses in Bravely Default 2So while playing Bravely Default 2 I accidentally a build that can first turn kill most endgame bosses. This was not the plan, and it trivialised the endgame to the same extent as if I&amp;rsquo;d just hacked in an infinite damage attack. Ooops. On the upside I&amp;rsquo;m kinda proud of the build so I decided to write this post explaining what it is and how it works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Control Dark Souls with a piano</title>
      <link>http://0800ben.com/how_to/control_dark_souls_with_a_piano/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://0800ben.com/how_to/control_dark_souls_with_a_piano/</guid>
      <description>Controlling Dark Souls with a Piano? But Why?So i&amp;rsquo;ve had this midi piano keyboard for a while now but I don&amp;rsquo;t use it all that much. This project was intended to give me an excuse to use the keyboard more, with the hope being that it could help make me better at hitting specific notes or maybe even CHORDS. It didn&amp;rsquo;t quite pan out that way as I played for like half an hour and then gave up but it&amp;rsquo;s the thought that counts!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
